Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Additional Photographs 5917 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Crown - Monarch (Mirzoeff) (Box 25, Folder 28)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 66; 1 photograph
- Cultural Committee 1962 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 67; 1 photograph
- Customs Meeting (Box 25, Folder 30)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 68; 2 photographs
- D-Day Rally, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 1 photograph
- Damascus Pension Meeting 7/21/1980 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 70; 3 photographs
- Dauman Displays Meeting 12/4/1985 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 71; 7 photographs
- Dauman Display Ratification Meeting 2/13/1987 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 72; 8 photographs
- Day in the Fur Market Nov. 1985 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 73; 9 photographs
- Dealers Section Meeting Nov. 24, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 74; 6 photographs
- Dealers Section Oct. 5, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 75; 12 photographs
- Dealers Section Meeting 11/1974 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 76; 3 photographs
- Dealers Section Negotiations Nov. 1976 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 77; 4 photographs
- Dealers Section Meeting 11/1979 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 78; 3 photographs
- Dealers Section Meeting 11/1982 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 79; 4 photographs
- DeGeorge Shop, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 80; 1 photograph
- Delegation to Salvadoran Consolate 3/1988 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 81; 1 photograph
- Democratic Platform Hearings 5/76, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 82; 19 photographs
- Democratic Platform Hearings 5/76, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  collection re-organized this was box 18, ff 83; 16 photographs
- Dental Day at Seton -- Oct. 1, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  was b18 ff84 -- 4 photographs
- Dental Panel Meeting -- Nov. 9, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  was b18 ff85 -- 2 photographs
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (1) (Box 26, Folder 3)
  was b18 ff86 -- 26 photographs
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (2) (Box 26, Folder 4)
  was b18 ff86 -- 17 photographs
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (1) (Box 26, Folder 5)
  was b18 ff87 -- 23 photographs
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (2) (Box 26, Folder 6)
  was b18 ff87 -- 16 photographs
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (1) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  was b18 ff88 -- 26 photographs
- Dinners, Affairs, etc. (2) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  was b18 ff88 -- 18 photographs
- District 1 - New England IFLWU (Box 26, Folder 9)
  was b18 ff89 -- 26 photographs
- District 2 IFLWU (Box 26, Folder 10)
  was b18 ff90 -- 4 photographs
- Division Board Mtg. W/WDIF Reps. -- 6/1977 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  was b18 ff91 -- 4 photographs
- Division Board Meeting -- 5/19/1980 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  was b18 ff92 -- 8 photographs
- Division Boards Political Action -- 6/16/1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  was b18 ff93
- Division Board Meeting -- Dec. 10, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  was b18 ff94 -- 5 photographs
- Dean Dixon (Box 26, Folder 15)
  was b18 ff95 -- 1 photograph
- Dubin Meeting -- Dec. 1967 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  was b18 ff96 -- 16 photographs
- Eastern Airlines Meeting and Picket Line (Box 26, Folder 17)
  was b18 ff97 -- 2 photographs
- Easton Meeting and Party -- 12/5/1969 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  was b18 ff98 -- 4 photographs
- Easton Christmas Party (Mt. Jewett) Dec. 1971 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  was b18 ff99 -- 4 photographs
- Easton Annual Meeting -- Dec. 8, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  was b18 ff100 -- EMPTY
- Easton Christmas Party -- Dec. 7, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  was b18 ff101 -- 18 photographs
- Easton, PA (Norelle - June - 1975) (Box 26, Folder 22)
  was b18 ff102 -- 9 photographs
- Eberle Picnic (Box 26, Folder 23)
  was b18 ff103 -- 5 photographs
- Eberle Ratification Meeting -- 1/1977 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  was b18 ff104 -- 7 photographs
- Eberle Safety Committee -- 2/1979 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  was b18 ff105 -- 1 photograph
- Eberle Shop Mtg. Aug./1982 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  was b18 ff106 -- 7 photographs
- Eberle Shop Meetings -- Sept.-Oct. 1982 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  was b18 ff107 -- EMPTY
- Eberle Tanning -- 4/1969 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  was b18 ff108
- Eberle Tanning -- Feb. 1971 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  was b18 ff109 -- EMPTY
- Eberle Tanning Meeting -- March 31, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  was b18 ff110 -- EMPTY
- Eberle Tanning Reopening Meetings -- Dec. 1982 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  was b18 ff111 -- 5 photographs; news clippings
- Eberle Tanning Sewage Unit (Box 26, Folder 32)
  was b18 ff112 -- 2 photographs; news clippings
- Eberle Tanning (Signing new agreement) -- Jan. 1974 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  was b18 ff113 -- 2 photographs
- Ecuadoria Labor Minister -- June 1975 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  was b18 ff114 -- 12 photographs
- Educational Directors (Box 26, Folder 35)
  was b18 ff115 -- 1 photograph
- Educational Directors, IFLWU (Box 26, Folder 36)
  was b18 ff116 -- 1 photograph
- ELBECO Luncheon -- Dec. 1977 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  was b18 ff117 -- 1 photograph
- ELCO Ratification Meeting -- March 25, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  was b18 ff118 -- 4 photographs
- Electrical Section Contract -- 7/1979 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  was b18 ff119 -- 3 photographs
- Electrical Section Meeting -- 5/29/1973 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  was b18 ff120 -- 1 photograph
- Electrical Section Meeting -- 1/16/1974 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  was b18 ff121 -- 2 photographs
- Electrical Section Meetings -- 3/29/1976 and 3/15/1976 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  was b18 ff122 -- 11 photographs
- Electrical Negotiations -- 3/1972 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  was b18 ff123 -- 3 photographs
- Electrical Section negotiations -- 6/1980 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  was b18 ff124 -- 3 photographs
- Electrical Section Negotiations -- 6/1983 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  was b18 ff125 -- 2 photographs
- Electrical Negotiations -- June 1986 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  was b18 ff126 -- 4 photographs
- Elkland Bowling Champions -- 1974 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  was b18 ff127 -- 1 photograph
- Constitution - Elkland - April 1969 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  was b18 ff128 -- 8 photographs
- Elkland Committee - March 1970 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  was b18ff129 -- 3 photographs
- Elkland Ratification Meeting - April 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  was b18ff130 -- 1 photographs
- Entertainers (Box 27, Folder 3)
  was b18ff131 -- 5 photographs
- Excise Tax Repeal Meeting - 2/9/1954 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  was b18ff132 -- 7 photographs
- Exec. Bd. Local I-FLM-FJC (Box 27, Folder 5)
  was b18ff133 -- 6 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting Nov. 1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  was b18ff134 -- 2 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting -- Nov. 10, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  was b18ff135 - 3 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting - June 1, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  was b18ff136 -- 2 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting - 6/7/1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  was b18ff137 -- 5 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting - 11/19777 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  was b18ff138 -- 2 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting - 4/1978 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  was b18ff139 -- 3 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting -- 4/18/1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  was b18ff140 -- 3 photographs
- Executive Board Meeting -- 3/16/1984 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  was b18ff141 -- 3 photographs
- Executive Board Outing (Box 27, Folder 14)
  was b18ff142 -- 8 photographs
- Executive Boards, Joint Meeting - 11/23/1967 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  was b18ff143 -- 5 photographs
- Exec. Bds. Jt. Meeting - 2/26/1968 -- "Heritage of Douglass and Dubois" (Box 27, Folder 16)
  was b18ff144 -- 9 photographs
- TV Program - Extinct Species - 12/29/1969 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  was b19ff1 -- 3 photographs; news clippings
- Farewell Dinner - Baratta - Martin-Morris June 9, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  was b19ff2 -- 5 photographs
- Finance Committee 1962 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  was b19ff3 -- 1 photograph
- Florida Reunion - 2/22/1978 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  was b19ff4 -- 12 photographs
- Florida Reunion -- 2/15/1979 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  was b19ff5 -- 2 photographs
- Florida Retirees Reunion -- 3/23/1982 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  was b19ff6 -- 10 photographs
- Florida Reunion - Feb. 2, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  was b19ff7 -- 4 photographs
- Florida Retirees Luncheon - 1986 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  was b19ff8 -- 3 photographs
- Florida Retirees Luncheon - Feb. 5, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  was b19ff9 -- 28 photographs
- Folman, Rina and Adolph (Box 27, Folder 26)
  was b19ff10 -- 2 photographs
- Luncheon Forum Eric Foner -- Nov. 18, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  was b19ff11 -- 2 photographs
- Forum - Drugs and Our Children -- January 29, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  was b19ff12 -- 1 photograph
- Forum - 1965 Elections - 10/20/1965 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  was b19ff13 -- 11 photographs
- Forum - Labor and the 88th Congress (Box 27, Folder 30)
  was b19ff14 -- 5 photographs
- Forum - Vietnam and Peace in Southeast Asia - 6/22/1965 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  was b19ff15 -- 6 photographs
- Bob Frank Opening -- Jan. 23, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  was b19ff16 -- 1 photograph
- Frankfurt Fur Fair -- April 1971 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  was b19ff7 -- 11 photographs
- Frankfurt Fur Fair - 4/1973 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  was b19ff18 -- 13 photographs
- Frankfurt Fur Fair - 4/1978 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  was b19ff19 -- 6 photographs
- Franklin Tanning Negotiations - 8/1977 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  was b19ff20 -- 1 photographs
- Franklin Tanning Christmas Party - 12/1980 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  was b19ff21 -- 2 photographs
- Franklin Tanning Committee - Nov. 1983 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  was b19f22 - 1 photograph
- Franklin Tanning Nominating Meeting - 4/17/1984 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  was b19ff23 -- 3 photographs
- Freedom Festival -- 2/10/1968 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  was b19ff24 -- 12 photographs
- Freedom Festival -- 2/22/1969 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  was b19ff25 -- 13 photographs
- Freedom Festival - March 13, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  was b19ff26 -- 11 photographs
- Fulton Fish Market Committee - 8/1975 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  was b19ff27 -- 1 photograph
- Fur and Leather Dept. Conference - Boston - Nov. 1958 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  was b19ff28 - 3 photographs
- Fur and Leather Council - Feb. 1970 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  was b19ff29 - 2 photographs
- Fur and Leather Conference - 4/1976 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  was b19ff30 -- 2 photographs
- Fur and Leather Conference - N.Y. Statler Hotel -- 6/27-28/1980 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  was b19ff31 -- 10 photographs
- Fur and Leather Dept. Conference -- 6/27-28/1980 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  was b19ff32 -- 7 photographs
- Fur and Leather Council Meeting - Feb. 17, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  was b19ff33 -- 8 photographs
- Fur Auction Picture (Box 27, Folder 50)
  was b19ff34 -- 1 photograph
- Fur Blenders Guild - Contract Signing - Oct. 18, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  was b19ff35 -- 4 photographs
- Fur Blending Negotiations - April 1985 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  was b19ff36 -- 4 photographs
- Fur Cleaning Negotiations - May, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  was b19ff37 -- 1 photograph
- Fur Conservation Institute - Repub. Platform (Box 27, Folder 54)
  was b19ff38 - 13 photographs
- Fur Dealers Negotiations - Dec. 1984 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  was b19ff39 -- 2 photographs
- Fur Divisions Meeting 3/27/1979 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  was b19ff40 -- 11 photographs
- Fur Division Membership Meeting 4/28/1981 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  was b19ff41 -- 9 photographs
- Fur Dressers and Dyers Membership Meeting 4/21/1972 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  was b19ff42 -- no picture (note)
- Fur Dresses and Dyers Division Meeting 5/4/1973 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  was b19ff43 -- 1 photograph
- Fur Dresses and Dyers Meetings -- Nov. 9, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  was b19ff44 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Dressers and Dyers Meeting -- 3/14/1975 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  was b19ff45 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Dressers and Dyers Membership Meeting -- 10/1975 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  was b19ff46 --
- Fur Dressers and Dyers Meeting -- 10/29/1976 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  was b19ff47 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Dressers and Dyers Division Meeting -- 4/1978 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  was b19ff48 -- 23 photographs
- Fur Dressers and Dyers Division Board Members - 5/1978 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  was b19ff49 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Dressing Negotiations - Nov. 1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  was b19ff50 - 17 photographs
- Fur Dressing Negotiating Committee - Nov. 1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  was b19ff51 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Dyers Meeting - 4/16/1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  was b19ff52 -- 2 photographs
- Fur Dyers and Blenders - 4/1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  was b19ff53 -- 5 photographs
- Fur Dyeing Negotiations - 2/1983 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  was b19ff54 -- 7 photographs
- Fur Expo -- May 1983 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  was b19ff55 -- 7 photographs
- Fur Fair - 3/1979 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  was b19ff56 -- 2 photographs
- Fur Fair - March 1980 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  was b19ff57 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Fair, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  was b19ff58 -- 10 photographs
- Fur Fair - March - April, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  was b19ff59 -- 21 photographs
- FIFC Conference -- Oct. 1966 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  was b19ff60 -- 1 photograph
- For Information of Fashion Council (Box 28, Folder 15)
  was b19ff61 -- 1 photograph
- Fur is for Life == Columbus, OH 1986 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  was b19ff62 -- 2 photographs
- Fur Lobby - Washington -- 4/15-17/1980 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  was b19f63 -- 6 photographs
- Fur Locals Meeting -- 6/1983 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  was b19ff64 -- 1 photograph
- FLM Executive Board Officers -- R. George, Jr.; N. Pressman; C. Williams (Box 28, Folder 19)
  was b19ff65
- FLM-FJC Holiday Party -- Dec. 18, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  was b19ff66 -- 3 photographs
- FLM Holiday Party -- 12/14/1984 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  was b19ff67 -- 3 photographs
- FLM Merger Meeting (Box 28, Folder 22)
  was b19ff22 -- 5 photographs
- FLM Retirees Center (Box 28, Folder 23)
  was b19ff69 -- 6 photographs
- FLM Retirees Meeting, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  was b19ff70 -- 5 photographs
- FLM Retirees Meeting -- Jan. 1988 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  was b19ff71 -- 3 photographs
- FLM Trustees Meeting (Box 28, Folder 26)
  was b19ff72 -- 5 photographs
- Fur Manufacturing Negotiations, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  was b19ff73 - 4 photographs
- FMEC Contract Signing - 3/1952 (Fur Merchants Employers Council) (Box 28, Folder 28)
  was b19ff74 -- 1 photograph
- FMEC Contract Signing - 10/1954 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  was b19ff75 -- 8 photographs
- FMEC Contract Signing - 3/1956 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  was b19ff76 -- 3 photographs
- Fur Merchants Employers Council Contract - 3/1962 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  was b19ff77 - 1 photograph
- Fur New York Meeting (Box 28, Folder 32)
  was b19ff78 - 2 photographs
- Fur Service Division Meeting -- 4/26/1973 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  was b19ff79 -- 2 photographs
- Fur Service Division Meeting - 3/18/1975 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  was b19ff80 -- 4 photographs
- Fur Service Division Membership meeting - 10/1975 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  was b19ff81 -- 1 photograph
- Fur Trappers NLRB Hearings - Dec. 1946 - Jan. 1947 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  was b19ff82 -- 2 photographs
- Furriers Jt. Council Bd. of Directors, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  was b19ff83 -- 1 photograph
- Furriers Joint Council CIA (Box 28, Folder 38)
  was b19ff84
- Furriers Joint Council Exec. Bd. 4/1979 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  was b19ff85 -- 4 photographs
- FJC Leaders (Box 28, Folder 40)
  was b19ff86 -- 3 photographs
- Furriers Joint Council and Local 150 Meeting - 10/30/1967 (Box 28, Folder 41)
  was b19ff87 - 1 photograph
- Furriers Joint Council Meetings Manhattan Center - (Box 28, Folder 42)
  was b19ff88 -- 23 photographs
- Furriers Joint Council Meeting - Union Hall (Box 28, Folder 43)
  was b19ff89 -- 10 photographs
- Furriers Joint Council Meeting - 2/17/1981 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  was b19ff90 -- 1 photograph
- Furriers Joint Council Meeting, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 45)
  was b19ff91 - 5 photographs
- Furriers Jt. Council Membership Committee, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 46)
  was b19ff92 -- 1 photograph
- Furriers Joint Council Retirees Luncheon -- 10/1979 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  was b19ff93 -- 13 photographs
- FJC Retirees Meeting -- 11/20/1985 (Box 28, Folder 48)
  was b19ff94 -- 8 photographs
- FJC Retirees Installation, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 49)
  was b19ff95 -- 6 photographs
- FJC Retirees Holiday Party -- Dec. 15, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  was b19ff96 -- 7 photographs
- Gellman Industries Shop Meeting - 11/19/1976 (Box 28, Folder 51)
  was b19ff97 -- 2 photographs
- Pix - R. George (Box 28, Folder 52)
  was b19ff98 -- 17 photographs
- Georgia Trapping - 2/1979 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  was b19ff99 -- 3 photographs
- Gibson Endorsement - April 1978 (Box 28, Folder 54)
  was b19ff100 -- 1 photograph
- GIVAT Haviva Meeting Jan. 1970 (Box 28, Folder 55)
  was b19ff101 -- 1 photograph
- Goldsmith Leather Shop Meeting (Box 28, Folder 56)
  was b19ff102 -- EMPTY
- Harold Goldstein - Furriers Joint Council (Box 28, Folder 57)
  was b19ff103 -- 6 photographs
- Gorman Tribute Dinner - Nov. 27, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 58)
  was b19ff104 -- 2 photographs
- Pedro Grant visit -- 5/1975 (Box 28, Folder 59)
  was b19ff105 -- 6 Photographs
- Greek Fur Workers Dinner Dance - 3/14/1987 (Box 28, Folder 60)
  was b19ff106 -- 6 photographs
- Grievance Board, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 61)
  was b19ff107 - 1 photograph
- William Gropper Birthday Party (Carl Sandburg) (Box 28, Folder 62)
  was b19ff108 -- 1 photograph
- Group Photos (Box 28, Folder 63)
  was b19ff109 -- 30 photographs
- Groups (Box 29, Folder 1)
  was b19ff110 -- 14 photographs
- Grove Press - Rally - April 1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  was b19ff111 -- 18 photographs --- 8/24/1970 - 1.Robin Morgan-dragged out of Grove
- Haitian Rally - April 27, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  was b19ff112 - 1 photograph
- Haitian Rally - Sept. 23, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  was b19ff113
- E.H. Hall - FLM Members at work (Box 29, Folder 5)
  was b19ff114 -- EMPTY
- E.H. Hall Members at work -- 1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  was b19ff115 EMPTY
- E.H. Hall Negotiations - 3/1980 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  was b19ff116 -- 2 photographs
- E.H. Hall Contract Settlement -- 3/1983 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  was b19ff117 -- 1 photograph
- E.H. Hall Nominating Meeting -- 4/1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  was b19ff118 -- 1 photograph
- E.H. Hall Holiday Party -- Dec. 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  was b19ff119 -- 3 photographs
- Harris, Charles and Ronca, Thomas - April 1977 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  was b19ff120 -- 1 photograph
- Harper and Row Contract Signing -- 5/6/1971 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  was b19ff122 -- 2 photographs
- Harper and Row Contract Signing - 5/6/1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Harper and Row Signing of contract -- 1971 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  was b19ff123 -- 4 photographs
- Health PAC Dinner - Moe Foner - 5/6/1985 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  was b19ff124 -- 5 photographs
- Janice Henke - FIT Wildlife Mgt. Class - 4/13/1984 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  was b19ff125 -- 5 photographs
- Hide Action Program (Box 29, Folder 17)
  was b19ff126 -- 2 photographs
- Sidney Hillman (Box 29, Folder 18)
  was b19ff127 -- 1 photograph
- Hinchcliff Lumber Negotiations - Aug. 1976 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  was b19ff128 -- 3 photographs
- Hinchcliff Lumber Negotiations, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  was b19ff129 -- 6 photographs
- Hinchcliff Picnic - 8/1978 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  was b19ff130 -- 12 photographs
- Hispanic Labor Committee -- 4/1977 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  was b19ff131 -- 1 photograph
- Morris Horn Award -- 1961 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  was b19ff132 -- 2 photographs
- Hospital visits - April 9-10, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  was b19ff133 -- 2 photographs
- Housewarming - Dec. 17, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  was b19ff134 -- 3 photographs
- Hudson's Bay Contract Signing - 5/1984 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  was b19ff135 -- 1 photograph
- Hudson's Bay Exercise Program (Box 29, Folder 27)
  was b19ff136 -- 3 photographs
- Hudson's Bay Negotiations -- Oct. 1983 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  was b19ff137 -- 3 photographs
- Hudson's Bay Ratification Meeting -- 12/7/1983 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  was b19ff138 -- 5 photographs
- Hudson's Bay Co. - Retirees and Committee (Box 29, Folder 30)
  was b19ff139 -- 3 photographs
- Hudyma Farewell, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  was b19ff140 -- 3 photographs
- Hudmya Farewell, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  was b19ff141 -- 1 photograph
- Hughes - Brees Delegation - 1/29/1952 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  was b19ff142 -- 4 photographs
- Impeachment Petitions (Box 29, Folder 34)
  was b19ff143 -- 1 photographs
- Import Meeting of Industry -- Nov. 10, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  was b19ff144 -- 2 photographs
- Individuals, Misc. (1) (Box 29, Folder 36)
  was b19ff145 -- 26 photographs
- Individuals, Misc. (2) (Box 29, Folder 37)
  was b19ff145 -- 34 photographs
- Installation - Joint Board Officers - 6/24/1958 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  was b19ff146 -- 2 photographs
- Installations of Officers - 6/26/1969 -- (1) (Box 29, Folder 39)
  was b19ff147 -- 26 photographs
- Installations of Officers - 6/26/1969 (2) (Box 29, Folder 40)
  was b19ff147 -- 3 photographs
- Installation Meetings -- May 1951 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  was b19ff148 -- 33 photographs
- Installation Meetings - 5/1953 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  was b19ff149 -- 13 photographs
- Installation Meetings - Local 88 & 64 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  was b19ff150 -- 9 photographs
- Int'l. Assoc. of Fish & Wildlife Agencies - Sept. 1983 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  was b19ff151 -- 3 photographs
- Int'l. conf. of Shoe and Leather -- July 1966 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  was b19ff152 -- 3 photographs
- IEB (Box 29, Folder 46)
  was b19ff153 -- 15 photographs
- IFLWU Convention Atlantic City 1948 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  was b19ff154 -- 1 photograph
- IFLWU Convention, 1950 (Box 29, Folder 48)
  was b19ff155 -- 3 photographs
- IFLWU Convention, 1952 (Box 29, Folder 49)
  was b19ff156 -- 9 photographs
- IFLWU Convention, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 50)
  was b19ff157 -- 23 photographs
- IFLWU Youth Conference, 1941 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  was b19ff100
- Int'l. Fur Trade Federation - Sept. 10, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  was b19ff159 -- 2 photographs
- Int'l. Paper Strikers - Lock Haven at Staff (Box 30, Folder 3)
  was b19ff160 -- 2 photographs
- ILPA Award - Tempo - 12/1969 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  was b19ff161 -- 1 photograph
- ILPA Meeting - Tempo Award June 26, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  was b19ff162 -- 3 photographs
- ILPA Award - Oct. 1973 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  was b19ff163 -- 4 photographs
- ILPA Award - Sept. 1974 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  was b19ff164 -- 4 photographs
- Israel Cultural Center (Box 30, Folder 8)
  was b19ff165 -- 14 photographs
- Italian Exhibit Basketball (Box 30, Folder 9)
  was b19ff166 -- 4 photographs
- Italian Exhibit - Football (Box 30, Folder 10)
  was b19ff167 - 15 photographs
- Italian Exhibit - Unused Material (Box 30, Folder 11)
  was b19ff168 -- 20 photographs
- Italian Leaders - Jt. Bd. (1) (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Italian Leaders - Jt. Bd. (2) (Box 30, Folder 13)
  was b19ff169 -- 25 photographs
- Italian Leaders - Jt. Bd. (3) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  was b19ff169 -- 19 photographs
- George Jackson's Pictures (Box 30, Folder 15)
  was b19ff170
- Sen Jacob Javits (Fur Imports) - Nov. 1967 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  was b19ff171 -- 5 photographs
- Jewish Stage Stars Perform for Fur Union Strikers; Maurice Schwartz; Aaron Leredoff (Box 30, Folder 17)
  was b20ff1 - 2 photographs
- Jobs for all Conference - 9/27/1975 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  was b20ff2 -- 2 photographs
- Joint Board Boat (Pinsley) (Box 30, Folder 19)
  was b20ff3 -- 1 photographs
- Joint Board Christmas Party, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  was b20ff4 -- 13 photographs
- Joint Board Xmas Party - Dec. 1967 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  was b20ff5 -- 11 photographs
- Joint Board Xmas Party - Dec. 23, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  was b20ff6 -- 15 photographs